<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<Reviews>
  <doc id="1">
    <rating>5</rating>
    <review>Excellent This app is super sonic solid mssngr, I love this application. Now me &amp; my frnds are always in touch. Thanxs team Full Review</review>
  </doc>
  <doc id="2">
    <rating>5</rating>
    <review>Perfecto Best chat application. Never adds unnecessary bloat ware like wechatt Full Review</review>
  </doc>
  <doc id="3">
    <rating>4</rating>
    <review>Gr8 Nice 1 Take too much time for loading d voice mail Full Review</review>
  </doc>
  <doc id="4">
    <rating>5</rating>
    <review>Such a great way to get your hands on the phone and the rest t world Thanks very good application I have been made use Full Review</review>
  </doc>
  <doc id="5">
    <rating>4</rating>
    <review>Good App The app works really well on android and kudos to the team who keep putting in new features. I just wanted to know why there was a limit of 50 in one group. Have heard that there is another version of the app on another platform that allows you more than 50 members...could you look at this option on android as well? Thanks... Full Review</review>
  </doc>
  <doc id="6">
    <rating>4</rating>
    <review>Request for some additions I would like to see birthday reminders in what'sapp so that we can wish them, date of birth while registration should be incorporated so that on their birth date registered in app we get notifications to which them Full Review</review>
  </doc>
  <doc id="7">
    <rating>5</rating>
    <review>A feedback on the "Chats" screen Hi. Just a little feedback. Could you add a feature to the "Chats" screen, where when I'm at the one of the last chats in the list, I can press the mast head saying "Chats" to move to the top of the list. I guess you have this feature for the iPhone. It'd be a small but useful addition. Full Review</review>
  </doc>
  <doc id="8">
    <rating>2</rating>
    <review>Look at other messaing apps It would be much better if it could be used on different platforms at the same time like skype or fb messanger. Full Review</review>
  </doc>
  <doc id="9">
    <rating>1</rating>
    <review>This app needs new version Since the last update, messages come with 10-20min delay. Full Review</review>
  </doc>
  <doc id="10">
    <rating>2</rating>
    <review>not opening at all. Very disappointed with this app. this is not at all opening after 4 months of successful use. i have also tried by reinstalling 2-3 times. but still no benefit. Full Review</review>
  </doc>
  <doc id="11">
    <rating>5</rating>
    <review>Cool app Its easy to connect with family and friend oh well its more like Voxer now ! Full Review</review>
  </doc>
  <doc id="12">
    <rating>1</rating>
    <review>No web client, cannot be used on multiple devices, won't install on 3g tablet... ... No web client, cannot be used on multiple devices, won't install on 3g tablet... Apart from these major drawbacks I quite like it... Full Review</review>
  </doc>
  <doc id="13">
    <rating>5</rating>
    <review>Awsome application It would be still better if the application had privacy settings so that we can avoid unauthorised use by unknown person.. There are person who can copy ptofile pic and misuse it.. Full Review</review>
  </doc>
  <doc id="14">
    <rating>2</rating>
    <review>I dont want to be charged for whatsapp Very sad about to have to pay to use whatsapp now. One morning I just woke ip and I was not allowed to send any messages. I may have hot loads of messages as well. But did not receive any. Unless I pay for it. With so many similars chat apps on the market I am sure millions of users eill migrate to another one Full Review</review>
  </doc>
  <doc id="15">
    <rating>4</rating>
    <review>Missing functions Never had an issues till recently with verssion2.11.3 on my HTC one. Can't access profile settings or start a group chat . Unable to locate a button on it. Please help?it use to be in the top right hand corner but all I have now are icons to start chat with one person n search. Full Review</review>
  </doc>
  <doc id="16">
    <rating>3</rating>
    <review>Hi Whatsapp is fun and nice to use to chat with my friends but my whatsapp expires next year. Is it possible to buy whatsapp for lifetime instead of just one/two years Full Review</review>
  </doc>
  <doc id="17">
    <rating>4</rating>
    <review>Good job guys. . .:) This app is really amazing. . .it keeps us in contacts. . .good job guys. . . Full Review</review>
  </doc>
  <doc id="18">
    <rating>5</rating>
    <review>Must have! Everyday I used this application and I love it! Keep it up WA Full Review</review>
  </doc>
  <doc id="19">
    <rating>5</rating>
    <review>Just love this app Its really a great one...i recommend all of them to use this app and keep in touch always by texting..sending videos..photos..voice messages etc... Full Review</review>
  </doc>
  <doc id="20">
    <rating>4</rating>
    <review>Plz help... :( I have lost my previous msg by reinstall.. and they are so special in my life.. I need them back...is that possible? Plz plz help :'( Full Review</review>
  </doc>
</Reviews>
